<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jon Tsiros</title><link>https://jtsiros.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Jon Tsiros</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 13:14:53 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jtsiros.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://jtsiros.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 13:14:55 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://jtsiros.github.io/resume/</guid><description>Resume I&amp;rsquo;m a software enthusiast that loves to build cool things, work with awesome people, and solve complex problems. I love building and leading software engineering teams that create robust business solutions that delight customers!
I have several years of experience in the software industry and I&amp;rsquo;ve worn many hats. Some of my proficiencies include: designing microservices and distributed systems, developing and debugging code, and designing cloud architectures.</description></item><item><title>Nest - An Implementation of the Nest API in Go</title><link>https://jtsiros.github.io/posts/go-nest-api/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 13:14:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://jtsiros.github.io/posts/go-nest-api/</guid><description>One of the first major open-source projects I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on in Go was to unify all of my home devices under the Home app provided by Apple&amp;rsquo;s iOS. I came to realize after acquiring many devices that there was just no universal solution to integrate these into Home. After doing some research and nifty network sniffing, most devices either had a published or unpublished RESTful API that I could implement along with Apple&amp;rsquo;s HAP specification.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jtsiros.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtsiros.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi! My name is Jon Tsiros, and I’m am a software engineer. I’ve created yet another tech blog to share my discoveries and passions for writing and developing software. I’m a huge Go advocate and love all things Go! Some of my goals for this blog are:
fmt.Println(` 1. Reinforce technical concepts through project examples and discussions 2. Provide resources to contribute back to the community and foster growth among engineers 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jtsiros.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jtsiros.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of my open-source projects. A majority of them can be found on Github.
Nest Nest is an implementation of the Nest API in Go.
MPExporter MPExporter exports your Macpass/Keepass compatible XML export file to CSV.
Dotfiles My dotfiles for fish, vim-go, neovim, and others.
Go + React An example Go application using Gotron + React</description></item></channel></rss>